<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://mclacks1.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://mclacks1.github.io/blog/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-23T13:52:59-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://mclacks1.github.io/blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Post]]></title>
    <link href="http://mclacks1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/23/first-post/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mclacks1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/23/first-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week 10:</p>

<p>This is our last week of class and I am beyond excited and mentally exhausted. Majority of my days, since I started this class, is spent trying to complete and correct assignments and projects that are somewhat complex, but it gives me an opportunity to be creative. I have learned a lot of information from this course and I enjoyed meeting all the different type of people from diverse backgrounds. Right now I am in a group with some very talented individuals that take pride in web development and graphic design and it is truly inspiring. I came up with a part of the project where I used my imagination with a fun spin on it. I got feedback from classmates and it was positive and made me feel like I was being a team player. So where ever this opportunity may take us I wish everyone well on their future endeavours. This has been a journey, more than like an adventure and I am forever grateful to be apart of YWEB because it has opened up doors for me. One more week until graduation!! Yesssss!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Post]]></title>
    <link href="http://mclacks1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/17/first-post/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-17T15:25:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mclacks1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/17/first-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week 9:</p>

<p>Two more weeks to graduation, today is my 24th birthday and this will be my first accomplishment since graduating from high school.Words can&rsquo;t express how happy I will be when this class is DONE!!! I remember when I first started this class and I was told that there will be times where you feel like you want to quit and your mental capacity will be exhausted to the fullest. I feel like that completely and I appreciate my instructors who are being flexible with everything that&rsquo;s going on with my personal life. I totally dislike the fact that we chnaged the classroom location, but I&rsquo;m dealing with it because class is almost over. Right now I am giving all that I have to remain focused and finish the course. I am doing my best to communicate with my case managers, instructors, and classmates. They are a great help with keeping me up to date with the new project that we just started. There are some very smart young men in the class with awesome ideas and I enjoy them sharing their advance knowledge and creativity.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
